[
    {
      "question": "2 + 2 = ?",
      "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
      "correctAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 * 3 = ?",
      "options": ["15", "10", "8", "20"],
      "correctAnswer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 - 4 = ?",
      "options": ["6", "7", "5", "8"],
      "correctAnswer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 รท 4 = ?",
      "options": ["3", "4", "5", "2"],
      "correctAnswer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 6 = ?",
      "options": ["14", "13", "15", "16"],
      "correctAnswer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 * 8 = ?",
      "options": ["56", "64", "49", "58"],
      "correctAnswer": "56"
    },
    {
      "question": "16 รท 4 = ?",
      "options": ["4", "6", "3", "5"],
      "correctAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 9 = ?",
      "options": ["11", "12", "13", "10"],
      "correctAnswer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "18 - 7 = ?",
      "options": ["10", "12", "11", "13"],
      "correctAnswer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 * 6 = ?",
      "options": ["36", "30", "42", "40"],
      "correctAnswer": "36"
    }
  ]
  